Guide to the Richard Hell Papers 1944-2003 (Bulk 1969-2003) MSS.140
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Photography
  - Subseries: B Personal Photography
    - 13 sleeves, color 4x6 photos and negatives, RH and Sheelagh, unidentified woman, Christmas, mid 1990s-2001 (Box Binder J, Folder f.)
    - 29 sleeves, color 4x6 photos and negatives, photos of monkey t-shirts, RH and Sheelagh on road trip, various locations including Elvis museum, undated (Box Binder K, Folder a.)
    - 30 sleeves, B&W 3x5 prints and negatives, color 4x6 photos and negatives, road trip, RH, Ruby and Sheelagh in various locations, including forest, hotel rooms, and others, undated (Box Binder K, Folder b.)
    - 7 sleeves, color 4x6 photos and negatives, RH, Ruby and unidentified others at Coney Island, New York, undated (Box Binder K, Folder c.)
    - 9 sleeves, color 3x 12 photos, color 3x5 photos, negatives, RH, Ruby and unidentified others, undated (Box Binder L, Folder a.)
    - 15 sleeves, color 4x6 photos and negatives, "South to Duke with Sheelagh", undated (Box Binder L, Folder b.)
    - 14 sleeves, color 4x6 photos, RH, Sheelagh, Ruby and Unidentified others in various locations, inc. NYC, undated (Box Binder M, Folder a.)
    - 14 sleeves, color 4x6 photos and negatives, RH, Sheelagh, grandmother, and Ruby in various locations outside of NYC, undated (Box Binder M, Folder b.)
    - 8 sleeves, B&W 4x6 photos, Ruby and unidentified boy, Christmas time, undated (Box Binder M, Folder c.)
    - 18 sleeves, color 4x6 photos, RH and Sheelagh in Paris, with unidentified others, 2002 (Box Binder N, Folder a.)
    - 6 sleeves, color 4x6 photos, RH, Sheelagh, and unidentified woman in Vermont, summer 2001 (Box Binder N, Folder b.)
    - 8 sleeves, color 4x6 photos, RH and unidentified others on movie set, coastal location, undated (Box Binder N, Folder c.)
    - 16 sleeves, color 4x6 photos, RH, Ruby and unidentified others in various locations including North Olmstead, Ohio, undated (Box Binder N, Folder d.)
    - 1 sleeve, 4 Polaroid images of RH and unidentified others, undated (Box Binder N, Folder e.)
    - 24 sleeves, 35mm negatives and contact sheets with no matching prints. RH, Sheelagh and unidentified others, undated (Box Binder O)
- Series VI: Artwork
  Various pieces of framed and mounted art work, by various artists.
  - Artwork Misc., undated (Box 21, Folder 1482)
  - Artwork-Richard Loves Robin, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 1483)
  - Artwork -self portrait-color photocopy, undated (Box 21, Folder 1485)
  - Artwork -Color marker portrait of RH, from Prudence, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 1486)
  - Artwork-Drawing Files & Flashback History Printouts, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 1487)
  - Artwork -Mercier, Lizzie, undated (Box 21, Folder 1488)
  - Artwork -Assorted Printouts, undated (Box 21, Folder 1489)
  - Artwork- Assorted Colored pencil drawings, artist unknown (5), ca.1983 (Box 21, Folder 1490)
  - Artwork- Assorted Colored pencil drawings, artist unknown (5), ca.1970 (Box 21, Folder 1491)
- Series VII: Friend's Manuscripts
  Manuscripts given to Richard Hell.
  - Bermudez, Josephine (Papers for intro to cinema), undated (Box 21, Folder 1492)
  - Bertei, AM; April; 1993 (Box 21, Folder 1493)
  - Brown, Lee Ann, Poems, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 1494)
  - Burdette, Nicole, "Busted", undated (Box 21, Folder 1495)
  - DeCapite, Mike, Excerpt from a novel in progress, letters undated (Box 21, Folder 1496)
  - DeCapite, Mike, Letters, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 1496)
  - DeCapite, Mike, Panino, Sketches of Rome and Florence, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 1497)
  - DeCapite, Mike, White Leather Notebook, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 1498)
  - DeCapite, Mike, "Through the Windshield with comments from Noah Lukeman", 1996 (Box 21, Folder 1499)
  - [EMPTY FOLDER] (Box 21, Folder 1500)
  - DeCapite, M.,Windshield, undated (Box 22, Folder 1501)
  - DeCapite,M, Tooth of Hope, undated (Box 22, Folder 1502)
  - DeCapite,M- Vegas, undated (Box 22, Folder 1503)
  - DeCapite,M, Untitled Partial, undated (Box 22, Folder 1504)
  - Dubris,M. Skels ½, undated (Box 22, Folder 1505)
  - DeCapite,M, Exc. Frm.Nov., undated (Box 22, Folder 1506)
  - Dubris,M, Maggie 2/2, undated (Box 22, Folder 1507)
  - Haasen,Richard & D.Cooper, undated (Box 22, Folder 1508)
  - Hawkins,R.,Wrath…, undated (Box 22, Folder 1509)
  - Holmstrom,J Legend…, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 1510)
  - James,A, Trrouble w/Par., 1994 (Box 22, Folder 1511)
  - Johnson,J, Incorrect Sadist, undated (Box 22, Folder 1512)
  - Johnson,J, Jody's Glass Eyeball, undated (Box 22, Folder 1513)
  - Katz,Vincent, undated (Box 22, Folder 1514)
  - Kaye,Lenny, undated (Box 22, Folder 1515)
  - McLaren,Malcolm,Surfing, undated (Box 22, Folder 1516)
  - Marks,J., undated (Box 22, Folder 1517)
  - Myles, Eileen, My Filmmaker, undated (Box 22, Folder 1518)
  - Myles,Eileen, My Filmmaker, undated (Box 22, Folder 1519)
  - Patton,W., Pages frm Journal, undated (Box 22, Folder 1520)
  - Nauen,E., American Guys, undated (Box 22, Folder 1521)
  - Dolle,Amy, Corpers, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 1522)
  - Dowell,A.& Schucht,R... Picnic, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 1523)
  - Rhodes,C., East Goes West…, undated (Box 22, Folder 1524)
  - Rhodes,C., Yearnings Toward…, undated (Box 22, Folder 1525)
  - Rose,C., Poems, undated (Box 22, Folder 1526)
  - Rower,A, undated (Box 22, Folder 1527)
  - Schuchat,S., Poems, undated (Box 22, Folder 1528)
  - Schuchat,S., Poems of Karpinsky, undated (Box 22, Folder 1529)
  - Schuchat,S., Hell "Poet & Punk", 1977 (Box 22, Folder 1530)
  - Schuyff, Peter, Neil McKeever, undated (Box 22, Folder 1531)
  - Seidelman,S., Desperately Seeking Susan, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 1532)
  - Sellers,T., "Acting Up w/ Annabelle, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 1533)
  - Szatmary,D., Punk Rock,Protes…, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 1534)
  - Zedd, Nick, Totem of the Depraved, undated (Box 22, Folder 1535)
  - Linden O, undated (Box 22, Folder 1536)
  - Stalking the Demon Lover, undated (Box 23, Folder 1537)
  - Strange German, Hell Script with Interviews, undated (Box 23, Folder 1538)
  - Anonymous, "Don't Judge a Man", undated (Box 23, Folder 1539)
  - Unidentified Poetry, undated (Box 23, Folder 1540)
  - Untitled Anonymous MS, undated (Box 23, Folder 1541)
  - Untitled/Anon. MS, "Joey G", undated (Box 23, Folder 1542)
  - Richard Hell Bio Pitch- Anon. Author, undated (Box 23, Folder 1543)
- Series VIII: Periodicals/ News Clippings
  - Subseries A: Flyers
    Flyers from Events.
    - Flyers- St.Marks Church- "Poets Banquet", undated (Box 23, Folder 1544)
    - Flyers -Madonnas & Whores, Veronica Vera Show, undated (Box 23, Folder 1545)
    - Flyers -La Mama, Etc., 1991 (Box 23, Folder 1546)
    - Flyers -Johnny Thunder, undated (Box 23, Folder 1547)
    - Flyers -Wetlands, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 1548)
    - Flyers -Unknown Venue, undated (Box 23, Folder 1549)
    - Flyers -Guillame Gollozzi, undated (Box 23, Folder 1550)
    - Flyers -Anders Tornberg Gallery, Sweden, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 1551)
    - Flyers -Gershwin Hotel, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 1552)
    - Flyers -Niagara, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 1553)
    - Flyers -Truck & Warehouse Theatre, Fame, undated (Box 23, Folder 1554)
    - Flyers - Question Productions, Halloween Party, undated (Box 23, Folder 1555)
    - Flyers -Rupert Goldsworthy Gallery, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 1556)
    - Flyers -Naked Angels, Theatre Programs, undated (Box 23, Folder 1557)
    - Flyers -Miller & Ringma, undated (Box 23, Folder 1558)
    - Flyers - Castelli Uptown, undated (Box 23, Folder 1559)
    - Flyers - The Kitchen, undated (Box 23, Folder 1560)
    - Flyers - Rizzoli Screening Room, Punking Out, undated (Box 23, Folder 1561)
    - Flyers -Stefanoti, undated (Box 23, Folder 1562)
    - Flyers -Le Palace backstage pass, undated (Box 23, Folder 1563)
    - Flyers - Fashion Moda, undated (Box 23, Folder 1564)
    - Flyers -Unions Square Galleried, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 1565)
    - Flyers -Cinema Classics,Zoe Lunde, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 1566)
    - Flyers - Anthology Film Archive, undated (Box 23, Folder 1567)
    - Flyers -Gracie Mansion Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 1568)
    - Flyers -Burden Gallery, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 1569)
    - Flyers -Klein Galleries, undated (Box 23, Folder 1570)
    - Flyers - Vinyl, undated (Box 23, Folder 1571)
    - Flyers - Fez "Neo-Karaoke", undated (Box 23, Folder 1572)
    - Flyers - Brooklyn Academy of Music, undated (Box 23, Folder 1573)
    - Flyers -Punking Out, Venue:MOMA, undated (Box 23, Folder 1574)
  - Subseries B: Periodicals/Tabloid
    Periodicals that Richard collected, includes both tabloids and magazines. Tabloids are paged by title, vol., no., and date information.
    - Periodicals - Almanach Actual, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 1575)
    - Periodicals - Art in America, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 1576)
    - Periodicals - BookForum- D.Cooper Review, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 1577)
    - Periodicals - Cream- Robert Quine, 1.9, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 1578)
    - Periodicals - Details- RH photo, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 1579)
    - Periodicals - RH Photo, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 1580)
    - Periodicals - Details- "Hell is For Heros", 1994 (Box 23, Folder 1581)
    - Periodicals - Downbeat- Robert Quince, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 1582)
    - Periodicals - Esquire- "Cool for Life", 2001 (Box 23, Folder 1583)
    - Periodicals - Fireworxaria, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 1584)
    - Periodicals - Here come the Martian Martins #3, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 1585)
    - Periodicals - Les Inrockuptibles #39, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 1586)
    - Periodicals - Kicks #2, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 1587)
    - Periodicals - Lozt #1- Photo of RH, undated (Box 23, Folder 1588)
    - Periodicals - The Minx #4 - (Monkey Quartet…), 1999 (Box 23, Folder 1589)
    - Periodicals - Mojo- Top 100 Punk Singles, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 1590)
    - Periodicals - Music Complex #8, undated (Box 23, Folder 1591)
    - Periodicals - Magician, Elvis Costello Interview., 1989 (Box 23, Folder 1592)
    - Periodicals - New Magazine #3, undated (Box 23, Folder 1593)
    - Periodicals - Paper- Just Say No, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 1594)
    - Periodicals - Punk 1.14, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 1595)
    - Periodicals - Punk #15, Top 99, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 1596)
    - Periodicals - The Rox, undated (Box 23, Folder 1597)
    - Periodicals - Sounds 13.9- RH Photo, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 1598)
    - Periodicals - Spin - "Sound Box", 2000 (Box 23, Folder 1599)
    - Periodicals - Vintage Violence #5, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 1600)
    - Periodicals - Wire #205, "Blank Generation", 2001 (Box 23, Folder 1601)
  - Subseries C: Clippings
    Clippings from various sources collected by Richard Hell.
    - Clippings- Celebration (misc), undated (Box 23, Folder 1602)
    - Clippings- Dear Reader Comic, Kooning, William, undated (Box 23, Folder 1603)
    - Clippings- DeSana, Jimmy, undated (Box 23, Folder 1604)
    - Clippings- Dylan, Bob, undated (Box 23, Folder 1605)
    - Clippings- Guitar Neck- Johnny Thunders, undated (Box 23, Folder 1606)
    - Clippings- Hannah, Daryl, Blade Runner, undated (Box 23, Folder 1607)
    - Clippings- Jungle D'Amerique, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 1607A)
    - Clippings- Manga, undated (Box 23, Folder 1608)
    - Clippings- Misc. Images, undated (Box 23, Folder 1609)
    - Clippings -Robert Quine, undated (Box 23, Folder 1610)
    - Clippings- Rotten, Johnny, undated (Box 23, Folder 1611)
    - Clippings- Tattoos, undated (Box 23, Folder 1612)
    - Clippings-Warhol, undated (Box 23, Folder 1613)
    - Clippings- Welles, Orson, undated (Box 23, Folder 1614)
    - Clippings- Wrestling, undated (Box 23, Folder 1615)
    - Clippings- Zippy, undated (Box 23, Folder 1616)
- Series IX: Artifacts and Objects
  - Black Russian Kahlua puzzle, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Pink t-shirt with image of monkey smoking a cigarette, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - White t-shirt with image of RH, “Richard Hell", undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Series X: Personal and Business Files
  - Subseries A: Financial
    Richard Hell’s Financial Records
    - Financial Records. Unemployment App., 1974 (Box 25, Folder 1617)
    - Financial Records. BMI Statements, 1983-1994 (Box 25, Folder 1618)
    - Financial Records. WB Royalties, 1985-1990 (Box 25, Folder 1619)
    - Financial Records. Columbia House Royalties, 1996-2001 (Box 25, Folder 1620)
    - Financial Records. Warner Chappel Royalties,1of2, 1991-1996 (Box 25, Folder 1621)
    - Financial Records. Warner Chappel Royalties,2of2, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 1622)
    - Financial Records.1of2, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 1623)
    - Financial Records. 2of2, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 1624)
    - Financial Records. -, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1625)
    - Financial Records. -, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 1626)
    - Financial Records. Receipts, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1627)
    - Financial Records. Japanese Tour Materials, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1628)
    - Financial Records. Japan Trip, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1629)
    - Financial Records. General, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1630)
    - Financial Records. 1of2, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 1631)
    - Financial Records. 2of2, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 1632)
    - Financial Records. Business & Receipts, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 1633)
    - Financial Records. 1of2, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 1634)
    - Financial Records. 2of2, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 1635)
    - Receipts, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 1636)
    - Receipts- 1of2, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 1637)
    - Receipts- 2of2, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 1638)
    - Financial Records. 1of3, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1639)
    - Financial Records. 2of3, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1640)
    - Financial Records. 3of3, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1641)
    - Financial Records. 1of3, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 1642)
    - Financial Records. 2of3, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 1643)
    - Financial Records. 3of3, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 1644)
    - Financial Records., 1997 (Box 26, Folder 1645)
    - Financial Records., 1998 (Box 26, Folder 1646)
    - Financial Records., 1999 (Box 26, Folder 1647)
    - Financial Records., 2001 (Box 26, Folder 1648)
    - Financial Records. –Personal, Budget, undated (Box 26, Folder 1649)
  - Subseries B: Legal
    Legal Records of Richard Hell’s court cases
    - Legal- Smyth/Meyer’s Court Case, 1986-1995 (Box 27A, Folder 1650)
    - Legal- Drivers License Suspension, 1988-1990 (Box 27A, Folder 1651)
    - Legal- Divorce, 1995 (Box 27A, Folder 1652)
    - Legal- Case w/ Gottehrer- Complaint, 2000 (Box 27A, Folder 1653)
    - Legal- Case w/ Gottehrer-Summons, 2000 (Box 27A, Folder 1654)
    - Legal- Case w/ Gottehrer-Motion to Dismiss, 2000 (Box 27A, Folder 1655)
    - Legal- Case w/ Gottehrer-Opposition's Affidavit, 2000 (Box 27A, Folder 1656)
    - Legal- Case w/ Gottehrer-Defendant's Affidavit, 2000 (Box 27A, Folder 1657)
    - Legal- Case w/ Gottehrer-Subpoena, 2000 (Box 27A, Folder 1658)
    - Legal- Case w/ Gottehrer-notice to Prudence, 2000 (Box 27A, Folder 1659)
    - Legal- Case w/ Gottehrer-Plaintiff’s Inter., 2000 (Box 27A, Folder 1660)
    - Legal- Case w/ Gottehrer-Def.Responses, 2000 (Box 27A, Folder 1661)
    - Legal- Case w/ Gottehrer-Correspondence& Notes, 2000 (Box 27A, Folder 1662)
    - Legal- Case w/ Gottehrer-Early Bckg. Detective., 1975-1990 (Box 27A, Folder 1663)
    - Legal- Case w/ Gottehrer-Royalty Statements., 1991-2000 (Box 27A, Folder 1664)
  - Subseries C: Personal
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access to this subseries requires approval of a Fales curator.
    - Personal-Selective Service Form, 1970 (Box 27B, Folder 1665)
      General
      Access to this subseries is restricted.
    - Personal- Address Book, ca..1974 (Box 27B, Folder 1666)
    - Personal- Address and Schedule Book, ca.1990 (Box 27B, Folder 1667)
    - Personal- Address notebook, undated (Box 27B, Folder 1668)
    - Personal- Address Book, undated (Box 27B, Folder 1669)
    - Personal- Address Book, undated (Box 27B, Folder 1670)
    - Personal- Appointment Book, 1983 (Box 27B, Folder 1671)
    - Personal- Appointment Book, 1985 (Box 27B, Folder 1672)
    - Personal- Appointment Book, 1986 (Box 27B, Folder 1673)
    - Personal- Appointment Book, 1987 (Box 27B, Folder 1674)
    - Personal- Appointment Book, 1988 (Box 27B, Folder 1675)
    - Personal- Appointment Book, 1989 (Box 27B, Folder 1676)
    - Personal- Appointment Book, 1990 (Box 27B, Folder 1677)
    - Personal-Business Cards w/addresses, undated (Box 27B, Folder 1678)
    - Personal- Notebook w/ add. & sched., undated (Box 27B, Folder 1679)
    - Personal- Calendar, 1979-1980 (Box 27B, Folder 1680)
    - Personal- Calendar 1982 (homemade) (Box 27B, Folder 1681)
    - Personal- Calendar 1982-EastVillageEye (Box 27B, Folder 1682)
    - Personal- Progress Report, Ruby Myers, 1993, 1994 (Box 27B, Folder 1683)
    - Wallet and related materials, undated (Box 28, Folder --)
      Personal, wallet items: Number of contents: 22. Contents: Two Tokyo Addresses, Traffic Ticket (1988), wax paper with writing, ACE playing card, photo, photo, St. Jude color drawing in plastic case, wallet size photo of Tando, Paris Address, misc. business cards, La Bota playing card, Bellevue Hospital Card, NY Eye and Ear Infirmary card.
- Series XII: Posters
  Posters collected by Richard Hell, some of his own design
  - Richard Hell and Voidoids, Destiny Street, Blindfish Promotion, Hamburg, undated (Box Mapcase,, Folder Drawer P)
  - Richard Hell and Wildchild, Paris, France, Mar 8, 1983 (Box Mapcase, Folder Drawer P)
  - Richard Hell and The Voidoids in concert, undated (Box Mapcase, Folder Drawer P)
  - Richard Hell and The Voidoids, Paris, France, February 4 (year unknown), undated (Box Mapcase, Folder Drawer P)
  - "The Facts of Death and the Truth about Eternity", by Richard Hell, and the "Truth about Eternity", by Richard Hell, for printing, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Film Posters, "The Blank Generation," A film by Amos "The Blank Generation," A film by Amos Poe and Ivan Kral, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Film Posters,"Dream Baby" Image from the Blank "Dream Baby" Image from the Blank Generation, by Stephanie Chernikowski, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Film Posters, Richard Hell introduces the Robert Bresson Richard Hell introduces the Robert Bresson film "The Devil Probably.", undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Film Posters, "Pandora’s Music 1836", A Doleen/Mojo "Pandora’s Music 1836", A Doleen/Mojo Production; Rotterdam, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Concert Posters, "Max’s Easter Rocky Festival Mailing, "Max’s Easter Rocky Festival Mailing, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Concert Posters, "The Heartbreakers" at CBGB’s, NYC "The Heartbreakers" at CBGB’s, NYC, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Concert Posters, "Television plus The Ramones at the Truck and Warehouse Theatre, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Concert Posters, "True Life presents Television at CBGB’s, "True Life presents Television at CBGB’s, NYC, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Concert Posters,"The Heartbreakers and the Ramones at New "The Heartbreakers and the Ramones at New Years Eve Champagne Party, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Concert Posters, Patti Smith and Television at Max’s Kansas City Smith and Television at Max’s Kansas City, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Concert Posters, Television appearing with Leather Secrets, Television appearing with Leather Secrets, at CBGB’s, NYC (with pencil drawing of nude woman on back), undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Book/ Reading Posters, Hanuman Books Presents, "A Reading of Poetry and Prose"; St. Marks Church, NYC, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Book/ Reading Posters, "Blank Generation revisited, the early days of punk rock," Shirman Books, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Book/ Reading Posters, "My name is Richard Hell, a no-singing all talking appearance…,presented by Lounge and Kinselas; Melbourne, Australia, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Book/ Reading Posters; Foam board mounted promo for "See Richard Hell Author of Go Now,"; at Summerstage, Central Park, NYC, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous; "Ultrasonic Superfunky Dancin’ Disco Party!!", Richard Hell as Celebrity Judge, at Squat Theatre, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous; "Richard Hell and the Voidoids, New Album Poster, "Destiny Street,; (4), undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, Signed poster: "To Raf, Go Now, with Hell"; drawing poster: "To Raf, Go Now, with Hell"; drawing by Richard Hell, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, Blue and Green glossy poster, "New Wave Rock n’ and Green glossy poster, "New Wave Rock n’ Roll," Sire Records, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, Glossy promotional poster for Richard Hell and The promotional poster for Richard Hell and The Voidoids, Japanese (2), undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous; "Richard Hell and the Voidoids," The Blank Generation, Promotional poster with image of Hell’s face, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Series XIII: Miscellaneous
  Miscellaneous materials from the Richard Hell papers.
  - Apollinaire- Mirabeau Bridge, undated (Box 31, Folder 1700)
  - Birds, undated (Box 31, Folder 1701)
  - Book Illustrations, undated (Box 31, Folder 1702)
  - Consumer questionnaire, blank, undated (Box 31, Folder 1703)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 31, Folder 1704)
  - Singer Mgmt- Publicity Shots, undated (Box 31, Folder 1705)
  - Reading List/ Want List, undated (Box 31, Folder 1706)
  - South of the Border, undated (Box 31, Folder 1707)
  - The Throbbers, undated (Box 31, Folder 1708)
  - The Way of Liberation, undated (Box 31, Folder 1709)
  - Wonderful Books, List 1,Trans., undated (Box 31, Folder 1710)
- Series XIV: Motion Picture Film Material
  - Subseries A: Access Copies
    Access copies may not be available. Please contact a Fales archivist.
    - Meet Theresa Stern: 17 minutes of The Theresa Stern Story - Answer Print (2007 Restoration), ID: 140.0345 (Reel 140.0345)
      Gauge: 16mm
      Black and White, Sound
      TRT: 00:19:00
      From 16mm original camera negative and mag track.
  - Subseries B: Originals
    Production elements for the 16mm films, “The Theresa Stern Story” and “Autocannibalism”. Access copies may not be available for consultation, please ask a Fales archivist.
    - 70 - 16mm film production elements and some paper documentation such as shot lists, lab and music track notes, and trim book., undated (Box 50, Media 140.0266 - 140.0272, Box 51, Media 140.0273 - 140.0279, Box 52, Media 140.0280 - 140.0286A, Box 53, Media 140.0287 - 140.0301, Box 54, Media 140.0302 - 140.0333, Box 55, Media 140.0334 - 140.0340A)
- Series XV: Videotape Recordings
  - Subseries A: Access Copies
    Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - Theresa Master 9/13/93, 1993; ID: 140.0352 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 140.0352)
      Format: DVD
      Duration: 00:18:00
      Original Format: 3/4" U-Matic
    - Meet Theresa Stern: 17 Minutes of The Theresa Stern Story (2007 Restoration), 1993; ID: 140.0348 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 140.0348)
      Duration: 00:19:00
    - Meet Theresa Stern, Writer/Director: Richard Meyers (aka Richard Hell), undated; ID: 140.0355 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 140.0355)
      Duration: 00:17:00
    - "Meet Theresa Stern" 18:33 mins. Richard Meyers, undated; ID: 140.0358 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 140.0358)
      Duration: [00:22:00]
    - Theresa (Stern) Rejected 1st Cut, Undated; ID: 140.0361 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 140.0361)
      Duration: [00:21:00]
    - Theresa Stern 1st Cut Better, undated; ID: 140.0364 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 140.0364)
      Duration: [00:19:00]
    - Meet Theresa Stern, 2007-02-08
  - Subseries B: Originals
    Consists of 72 analog videorecordings. Works include: Meet Theresa Stern, Blank Generation, and Rebels: A Journey Underground, which includes a 1998 interview with Richard Hell. The videotapes also include various music videos and tribute performances by Hell and others. Access copies may not be available for consultation, please ask a Fales archivist.